const questions = [
    {
      question: "If I see an accident at work, I should",
      options: ["Talk to the person involved", "Ignore it because it’s none of my business", "Feel sorry for the person", "Tell my supervisor"],
      correct: "Tell my supervisor"
    },
    {
      question: "Most back injuries at work are caused by:",
      options: ["Automobile accidents", "Improper lifting", "Weak muscles", "Old age"],
      correct: "Improper lifting"
    },
    {
      question: "Electrical shock can cause",
      options: ["Hearing loss", "Death", "Blindness", "Chemical sensitivity"],
      correct: "Death"
    },
    {
      question: "Before plugging in an electrical tool or appliance, you should",
      options: ["Check for broken plug", "Check for exposed wires", "Don’t overload an outlet", "All of the above"],
      correct: "All of the above"
    },
    {
      question: "If the ground prong is missing from the equipment plug,",
      options: ["You may use the equipment if you are careful", "You may use the equipment if you have permission", "You may not use the equipment", "You must be a supervisor to use the equipment"],
      correct: "You may not use the equipment"
    },
    {
      question: "Equipment Operating instructions are",
      options: [
        "For new employees",
        "Only guidelines",
        "Specific steps to follow every time",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      correct: "Specific steps to follow every time"
    },
    {
      question: "The emergency stop button is for",
      options: [
        " Normal starting and stopping of equipment",
        "Only for managers and supervisors",
        "For me to use if someone is caught in a machine",
        "Only for Fire Department Use"
      ],
      correct: "For me to use if someone is caught in a machine"
    },
    {
      question: "When should ladders be inspected?",
      options: [
        "Each day before use",
        "At least once a week",
        "At least once a month",
        "Annually"
      ],
      correct: "Each day before use"
    },
    {
      question: "On the multi-colored chemical label, Red represents",
      options: [
        "Fire Hazard",
        "Health Hazard",
        "Reactivity Hazard",
        "Personal Protective Equipment"
      ],
      correct: "Health Hazard"
    },
    {
      question: "When lifting, I should NOT",
      options: [
        "Look directly ahead",
        "Twist at the waist",
        "Wear shoes",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      correct: "Twist at the waist"
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  